AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records 5478
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records
1912-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO)
AFL-CIO. Railway Employees' Department (RED)
5478
149 cubic feet
149 linear ft.
Records (documents).
This collection is primarily the correspondence (carbons and originals), of the RED Presidents: B.M. Jewell, Fred N. Aten, and Michael Fox, with officers of RED affiliated unions and the carriers. Also, included are minutes and proceedings, legal records, financial records, legislative materials, circulars, publications, reports, case files, statistical data and clippings.
3119629
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 20, 1976
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 13, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Against a background of rapid rail expansion, begun in the late 1800's, organized railway labor appeared and began to flourish throughout the first decades of the 20th Century. This expansion
was facilitated in 1908 by the formation of the Railway Employees' Department (RED) of the American Federation of Labor (AFL) - a cooperative effort on the part of seven national shop craft unions, the Brotherhood of Carmen of America; International Association of Machinists; International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers and Helpers; International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders and Helpers of America; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; International Brotherhood of Firemen, Oilers Helpers, Roundhouse and Railway Shop Laborers; and Sheet Metal Workers International Association. Materials relating to the International Association of Machinists, and the Brotherhood of Carmen of America predominate.
RED bargained with the Railroad Carriers for these skilled trade employes on a wide range of activities affecting almost every aspect of their social and economic status as employees. RED was active as in organizing, collective bargaining, legislation, apprentice training, political lobbying (especially the encouragement of active involvement of rank and file in political activities), and the protection of job opportunities of these railroad workers. The RED endeavored to guarantee every member representation, to preserve craft autonomy, and to provide for joint federated action through unity of purpose and increased economic strength.
Scope and Contents
This collection is primarily the correspondence (carbons and originals), of the RED Presidents: B.M. Jewell, Fred N. Aten, and Michael Fox, with officers of RED affiliated unions and the carriers. Also, included are minutes and proceedings, legal records, financial records, legislative materials, circulars, publications, reports, case files, statistical data and clippings.
Of the 377 national railroads represented in the records, eighteen emerge as major, these are the Atlantic Coast Line Railroad; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad; Boston and Maine Railroad; Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad; Chicago and Northwestern Railroad; Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad; Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad; Long Island Railroad, Louisville and Nashville Railroad; Michigan Central Railroad; Missouri, Kansas and Texas Railroad; New York Central Railroad; New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad; Norfolk and Western Railroad; Northern Pacific Railway; Pennsylvania Railroad; Southern Pacific Railroad; and Union Pacific Railroad. The collection deals almost exclusively with the American railroads, although there are some materials concerning three major Canadian railroads: Canadian Railway, Canadian Northern Railway, and Canadian Pacific Railway.
The collection materials are organized into 31 series.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5366: American Federation of Labor, Railway Employees Department vs. Union Pacific Railroad Company, Hanson et al. Records 5478 mf: AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records on Microfilm
Arrangement
Series I: Jurisdiction, 1926-1947
Series II: Seniority, 1920-1940
Series IIIa: Organizing, 1918-1954
Series IV a: International Organizations, American Federation of Labor - Union Affiliated with the AFL, 1912-1961
Series Va: American Federation of Labor, Departments Other Than This Department and State Federations of Labor, 1941-1968
Series VI: Railroad Employees' Department Credentials, 1934-1938
Series VII a: American Federation of Railway Workers and Other Outside Organizations - Not Affiliated with the American Federation of Labor, 1927-1953
Series VIII a: System Federations and Matters Pertaining to Individual System Federations, 1917-1961
Series IX: Convention Files, 1922-1959
Series XXVIIa: Executive Council - Minutes and Correspondence, 1921-1961
Series X: Department Circulars - Informational Circulars Sent to General Chairman on Systems Federations from Department Headquarters, 1945-1964
Series XI: Federal Apprenticeship Training - Files
Series XXIX: Financial Materials - Invoices, 1923-1970
Series XII: Political Matters - Correspondence, Campaign Material and Minutes Relevant of the National Congressional Election, 1932-1965
Series XIII: Transportation Act, 1921-1928
Series XIV: Interstate Commerce Commission, 1923-1966
Series XXVIII: Correspondence RE: Board of Adjustments, 1923-1946
Series XV: Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964
Series XVI: Federal Affairs - Consolidation, Retirements, Pensions, ICC, Waterways, Ex Parte 171, Emergency Railway Legislation, etc., 1928-1970
Series XVII: National Railroad Adjustment Board - Legislation, Correspondence, Reports, Minutes, Etc., 1933-1970
Series XXX: Railroad Unemployment Insurance
Series XXXI: Fair Labor Standards Act
Series XVIII: Consolidations, Mergers, Reorganizations and Abandonments, 1938-1970
Series XIX: Co-Operation - Financial Matters, Minutes, Proceedings and Correspondence, 1919-1933
Series XXIII: National Rules and Working Conditions Agreements Between Employees Represented by the Railway Employees Department of the AFL and Carriers Under the Provisions of the Transportation Act of 1920 - Correspondence, Etc., 1920- 1934
Series XXIV: 14B Files
Series IIIb: Organizing, 1918-1954
Series IVb: International Organizations, American Federation of Labor - Union Affiliated with the AFL, 1912-1961
Series Vb: American Federation of Labor, Departments Other Than This Department and State Federations of Labor, 1941-1968
Series VIIb: American Federation of Railway Workers and Other Outside Organizations - Not Affiliated with the American Federation of Labor, 1927-1953
Series VIIIb: System Federations and Matters Pertaining to Individual System Federations, 1917-1961
Series XXVIIb: Executive Council - Minutes and Correspondence, 1921-1961
Series XXV: Railroad Employees' Department-Master File of Official Circulars, 1916-1867
Railroads. Employees. Labor Unions. United States. Sources; Allen, Leo Elwood, 1898-; Anderson, Herman Carl, 1897-; Arens, Henry Martin, 1873-1963.; Aten, Fred N.; Atterbury, William W. (William Wallace), 1916-1995; Ayers, William Augustus, 1867-1952.; Bachman, Nathan Lynn, 1878-1937.; Bailey, Cleveland Monroe, 1866-1965.; Berkley, Alben William, 1877-1956.; Beyer, O. J.; Biemiller, Andrew J. (Andrew John), 1906-1982; Blatnik, John A., 1911-1991; Brown, Clarence J., 1893-1965; Burns, J.M.; Burnside, Maurice Gwinn, 1902-1991; Byrnes, John William. 1913-; Capper, Arthur, 1865-1951; Carter, Charles David, 1868-1929.; Chase, Ray P. (Ray Park), 1880-1948; Chiperfield, Robert Bruce, 1899-1971.; Christianson, Theodore, 1883-1948.; Christopher, George Henry, 1888-1959; Cole, David L. (David Lawrence), 1902-1978.; Corning, Parker, 1874-1943.; Crosser, Robert, 1874-1957.; Cunningham, Paul Harvey, 1890-1961.; Curtis, Charles. 1860-1936.; Davis, Glenn R. (Glenn Robert), 1914-1988; Davis, James J. (James John), 1873-1947.; Deane, Charles Bennett, 1898-1969.; Delaney, James Joseph, 1901-; Dieterich, William Henry, 1876-1940.; Dolliver, James I. (James Isaac), 1894-1978; Fess, Simeon D. (Simeon Davidson), 1861-1936; Ford, Gerald, 1913-; Fox, Michael; Franklin, J. A.; Fullbright, James Franklin, 1877-1948; Garber, Milton Cline, 1867-1948; Good, N. P.; Green, Theodore Francis, 1867-1966; Gross, H. R. (Harold Royce), 1899-1987; Hagen, Harold C. (Harold Christian),1901-1957; Harding, Warren G. (Warren Gamaliel), 1865-1923; Hastings, William Wirt, 1866-1938; Havenner, Frank Roberts, 1882-1967; Hawes, Harry Bartow, 1869-1947; Hedrich, Erland Harold, 1894-1954; Herter, Christian Archibald, 1895-1966; Hoeven, Charles B. (Charles Bernard), 1895-1980; Hoidale, Einar, 1870-1952; Holland, Spessard L. (Spessard Lindsey), 1892-1971; Hooper, Benjamin; Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964; Huddleston, George, 1869-1960; Hull, Merlin, 1870-1953; Humphrey, Hubert H. (Hubert Horatio), 1911-1978; Jeffrey, Harold; Jensen, Benton Franklin, 1892-1970; Jewell, Bert M., 1881-1968; Johnson, Magnus, 1871-1936; Judd, Walter H., 1898-1994; Keating, Edward, 1875-1965; Kee, John, 1874-1951; Keefe, Frank B., 1887-1952; Kelly, Edward Austin, 1892-1969; Kilgore, Harley Martin, 1893-1956; Knutson, Harold, 1880-1953; Kvale, Paul John, 1896-1960; La Follette, Robert M. (Robert Marion), 1895-1953; LeCompte, Karl Miles, 1887-1958; Lehlbach, Frederick R.(Frederick Reimold), 1876-1937; Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., 1902-1985; Lozier, Ralph F. (Ralph Fulton), 1866-1945; Lucas, Scott Wike, 1892-1968; Lundeed, Ernest, 1878-1940; Lyle, John E. (John Emmett),1910-2003; Madden, Ray J. (Ray John), 1892-1987; Major, Samuel C. (Samuel Collier), 1869-1931; Manlove, Joe Jonathan, 1876-1956; Marshall, Fred, 1906-1985; Martin, Thomas E. (Thomas Ellsworth), 1893-1971; McCarthy, Eugene J., 1916-2005; McClintic, James Vernon, 1878-1948; McKeown, Tom D. (Tom Deitz), 1878-1951; McSweeny, John, 1890-1969; Michener, Earl Cory, 1876-1957; Milligan, Jacob Le Roy, 1889-1951; Morris, Toby, 1899-1967; Murray, Philip, 1886-1952; Murray, Reid Fred, 1889-1952; Neely, Matthew Mansfield, 1874-1958; Newton, Walter H., 1880-1941; O'Hara, Joseph Patrick, 1895-1958; O'Konski, Alvin E. (Alvin Edward),1904-1987; Oldfield, William Allan, 1874-1928; Parks, Tilman Bacon, 1872-1950; Pepper, Claude, 1900-1989; Rae, Samuel; Rainey, Henry Thomas, 1860-1934; Ramsey, Robert Lincoln, 1877-1956; Reed, James Byron, 1881-1935; Robinson, Joseph Taylor. 1872-1937; Romjue, Milton Andrew, 1874-1968; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945; Rubey, Thomas Lewis, 1862-1928; Sabath, Adolph Joachim, 1866-1952; Saltonstall, Leverett, 1892-1979; Schall, Thomas D. (Thomas David), 1878-1935; Shelly, John Francis, 1905-; Shipstead, Henrik, 1881-1960; Shoemaker, Francis Henry, 1889-1958; Smith, Lawrence Henry, 1892-1958; Sparkman, John Jackson, 1899; Staggers, Harley Orrin, 1907-; Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing), 1900-1965; Swank, Fletcher B., 1875-1950; Talle, Henry Oscar, 1892-1969; Thomas, John William Elmer, 1876-1965; Thompson, J. W.; Tillman, John Newton, 1859-1929; Trammell, Park, 1876-1936; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972; Vandenburg, Arthur Hendrick; Wadsworth, James J. (James Jeremiah), 1905-1984; Wagner, Robert F. (Robert Ferdinand), 1877-1953; Werdel, Thomas Harold, 1905-1966; Wier, Roy William, 1888-1963; Willard, Daniel; Willis, Frank B.(Frank Bartlette),1871-1928; Wingo, Otis Theodore, 1877-1930; Withrow, Gardner Robert, 1892-1964; Wolff, Joseph Scott, 1878-1958; Zablocki, Clement John, 1912-1983; AFL-CIO; AFL-CIO. Railway Employees' Department.; American Federation of Railroad Workers; American Railway Supervisors Association; Association of Colored Railway Trainmen and Locomotive Firemen; Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway Company; Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company; Boston and Maine Railroad; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees.; Brotherhood of Railroad Shop Crafts of America; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes; Canadian National Railways; Canadian Northern Railway Company; Canadian Pacific Railway Company; Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company; Chicago and North Western Railway Company; Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Company (1866-80); Citizens Committee for Industrial Americanism; Cooperating (Non-operating) Railroad Labor Organizations; Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Company; Foremen's Association of America; International Association of Machinists; International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers, and Helpers; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers.; International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; International Union of Operating Engineers; Kansas City Southern Railway Company; Lehigh Valley Railroad Company; Long Island Rail Road; Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company; Michigan Central Railroad Company; Missouri Pacific Railroad Company; Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad; New York Central Railroad Company; New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Company; New York, Chicago & St. Louis Railroad; Norfolk and Western Railway Company; Northern Pacific Railroad Company; Order of Railroad Telegraphers (U.S.); Pennsylvania Railroad; Progressive Railway Union; Pullman Car Company; Railway Labor Management Committee; Railway Labor's Political League; Reading Company; Sheet Metal Workers' International Association; Southern Pacific Clerks; Southern Pacific Company; Telegraph Workers Independent Union; Union Pacific Railway Company; United States. Interstate Commerce Commission.; United States. National Housing Agency.; United States. National Mediation Board; United States. National Railroad Adjustment Board.; United States Railroad Labor Board.; United Welders of America
3119629
- Series I: Jurisdiction, 1926-1947
  Scope and Contents
  Chiefly correspondence (carbons and originals) between various officers of unions affiliated with RED concerning jurisdictional disputes. Also, listings of confrontations; appeals to RED for resolution; cooperative agreements between unions; RED Executive
  - Jurisdictional Agreements, 1926-1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Code No. 1-0, pt. 1; July 17, 1926 - Dec. 31, 1937
  - Jurisdictional Agreements, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Code No. 1-0, pt. 2; Jan 1938 - Dec. 30 1939
  - Southern Railway System, 1927-1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Code No. 1-279; Feb. 26, 1927 - Mar. 3, 1947
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1927-1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Code No. 1-286; April 1, 1927 - June 3, 1947
- Series II: Seniority, 1920-1940
  Chiefly correspondence (carbons and originals) between major union leaders Jewell, J.W. Thompson (President, Grand Trunk System Federation, No.92), G.H. Stewart (President, System Federation No. 41), W.H. Gorman (General Chairman of Machinists, Chesapeake
  - Southern Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Code No. 2-222; Mar. 21, 1921 - May 24, 1922
  - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1920-1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Code No. 2-604; Mar. 4, 1920-July 30, 1940
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1925-1927 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Code No. 2-613; April 20, 1925 - Feb. 1927(?)
  - Young vs. Canadian Northern Railway Co., 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Code No. 2-638; Feb. 3, 1930 - Jan. 15, 1931
  - Grand Trunk Western Railroad, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Code No. 2-640; July 9, 1928 - Mar. 5, 1929
- Series IIIa: Organizing, 1918-1954
  Chiefly correspondence (carbons and originals) between officers of RED unions and the Executive Council of RED - Jewell, and J.M. Burns (Secretary-Treasurer) - regarding union organization on the railroads. Also, constitutions, contracts, relevant legisla
  - Railway Employee's Dept. Affiliation, 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Code No. 8-24; June 25, 1920 - Aug. 31, 1922
  - Harry S. Jeffrey, Appellant, vs. AFL, International Association of Machinists, Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders and Helpers of America, 1918- 1926 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Code No. 8-64; Sept. 16, 1918 - Aug. 10, 1926
  - Seven International Organizations Referring Black Helpers to Shop Craft Mechanics, 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Code No. 8-112; Dec. 15, 1922 - Jan. 9, 1926
  - Michigan Central Railroad, 1923-1929 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Code No. 8-118; Mar. 26, 1923 - Mar. 4, 1929
  - Illinois Central Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Code No. 8-121; Jun. 2, 1923 - Nov. 21, 1934
  - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1923-1933 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Code No. 8-129; June 18, 1923 - Jan. 17, 1933
  - International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1924-1927 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Code No. 8-129a; Aug. 4, 1924 - Feb. 5, 1927
  - Nashville, Chattanooga and St. Louis Railroad, 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Code No. 8-131; Oct. 25, 1933 - Jan. 10, 1935
  - New York Central Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Code No. 8-132; Nov. 3, 1923 - Dec. 14, 1934
  - Northern Pacific Railway, 1927-1934 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Code No. 8-134; Jan. 5, 1927 - Dec. 17, 1934
  - Georgia and Florida Railroad, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Code No. 8-136; Aug. 18, 1933 - May 29, 1934
  - Erie Railroad, 1925-1934 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Code No. 8-138; July 21, 1925 - July 25, 1934
  - Erie Railroad, Sheet Metal Workers in the Maintenance of Way Department, 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Code No. 8-138a; July 18, 1927 - Feb. 14, 1928
  - Central Vermont Railway, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Code No. 8-141, Sec 2; Mar. 2, 1933-Mar. 9, 1934
  - Alabama, Tennessee and Northern Railway, 1923-1934 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Code No. 8-145; May 5, 1923 - Feb. 9, 1934
  - New York, Ontario and Western Railroad, 1923-1937 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Code No. 8-146; Mar. 20, 1923 - Aug. 9, 1937
  - Galveston, Houston and Henderson Railway, 1923-1937 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Code No. 8-147; May 16, 1923 - April 27, 1937
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line Railroad, 1923-1945 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Code No. 8-148; May 10, 1923 - Jun. 11, 1945
  - Gulf, Mobile and Northern Railway, 1922-1934 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Code No. 8-150; Oct. 25, 1922 - July 31, 1934
  - Georgia Railroad, 1922-1936 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Code No. 8-151; Oct. 1, 1922 - Apr. 22, 1936
  - International Great Northern Railway Co., 1923-1936 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Code No. 8-152; Sept. 1, 1923 - July 21, 1936
  - Minneapolis and St. Louis Railway, 1929-1934 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Code No. 8-153; Aug. 8, 1929 - Nov. 16, 1934
  - Norfolk Southern Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Code No. 8-154; Jun. 4, 1923 - Sept. 19, 1934
  - Spokane, Portland and Seattle Railway, 1923-1934 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Code No. 8-155; Jun. 4, 1923 - July 5, 1934
  - Burlington-Rock Island Railroad, 1923-1930 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Code No. 8-156; Apr. 29, 1923 - Feb. 7, 1930
  - Southern Pacific Railroad, 1923-1929 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Code No. 8-158, pt. 1-a; Sept. 21, 1923 - Mar. 29, 1929
  - Southern Pacific, 1928-1934 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Code No. 8-158, pt. 3; Feb. 27, 1928 - May 10, 1934
  - Forth Worth and Denver City Railroad, 1923-1935 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Code No. 8-159; Sept. 30, 1923 - Jan. 28, 1935
  - Railway Employee's Department-Organizing Campaign, 1923-1933 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Code No. 8-160, pt. 1; Oct. 1923 - Aug. 1933
  - Railway Employee's Department-Organizing Campaign, 1933-1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Code No. 8-160, pt. 2; Aug. 23, 1933 - Dec. 31, 1942
  - Railway Employee's Department-Pro-Rated Bills, 1950-1954 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Code No. 8-160; Feb. 16, 1950 - Dec. 20, 1954
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Code No. 8-164, pt. 2; Nov. 8, 1933 - Aug. 10, 1934
  - Kansas City Southern Railway, 1924-1938 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Code No. 8-165, pt. 1; Feb. 29, 1924 - Oct. 31, 1938
  - Kansas City Southern Railway, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Code No. 8-165, pt. 2; Oct. 31, 1938 - Jan. 20, 1939
  - Buffalo Creek Railroad, 1923-1936 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Code No. 8-166; May 5, 1923 - June 5, 1936
  - Missouri, Kansas and Texas Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Code No. 8-167; Oct. 15, 1923 - Oct. 24, 1934
  - Virginian Railway Company, 1923-1937 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Code No. 8-168; Oct. 18, 1923 - Aug. 4, 1937
  - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1924-1933 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Code No. 8-170, pt. 1; May 16, 1924 - Dec. 28, 1933
  - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Code No. 8-170, pt. 2; Dec. 13, 1933 - Jan. 27, 1934
  - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad - Special, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Code No. 8-170; Jan. 24, 1934 - Sept. 12, 1934
  - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1934-1941 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Code No. 8-170, pt. 3; Jul. 1, 1934 - Mar. 19, 1941
  - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad, 1922-1934 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Code No. 8-171; Oct. 6, 1922 - Aug. 16, 1934
  - Norfolk and Western Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Code No. 8-172; Sept. 6, 1923 - Jun. 29, 1934
  - Norfolk and Western Railroad, 1934-1938 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Code No. 8-172, pt. 2; Jul. 1934 - Jul. 19, 1938
  - Great Northern Railway, 1926-1934 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Code No. 8-173, pt. 2; Nov. 19, 1926 - Jun. 15, 1934
  - Great Northern Railway, 1934-1947 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Code No. 8-173, pt. 3; Jul 1, 1934 - Oct. 28, 1937
  - Great Northern Railway, 1937-1945 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Code No. 8-173, pt. 4; Nov. 1, 1937 - Jul. 6, 1945
  - Northwestern Pacific Railway, 1928-1934 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Code No. 8-174; Apr. 16, 1928 - Apr. 13, 1934
  - Atlanta (Joint) Terminal & Atlanta Terminal, 1929-1935 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Code No. 8-175; Sept. 19, 1929 - Mar. 8, 1935
  - Kentucky and Indiana Terminal, 1929-1941 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Code No. 8-176; Sept. 17, 1929 - Feb. 26, 1941
  - Central Railroad of New Jersey, 1926-1934 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Code No. 8-177; Aug. 17, 1926 - Sept. 24, 1934
  - Lehigh and New England, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Code No. 8-178; Oct. 18, 1934 - Dec. 27, 1934
  - Charleston and Western Carolina Railroad, 1930-1934 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Code No. 8-179; Feb. 1, 1930 - Mar. 2, 1934
  - Atlanta, Birmingham and Coast Railroad, 1924-1934 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Code No. 8-180; Feb. 7, 1924 - Jun. 29, 1934
  - Atlanta, Birmingham and Coast Railroad, 1924-1934 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Code No. 8-180, pt. 2; Jun. 28, 1934 - Oct. 29, 1940
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway, 1925-1934 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Code No. 8-182; Sept. 16, 1925 - Oct. 3, 1934
  - Florida East Coast Railroad, 1922-1934 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Code No. 8-183; Jul. 14, 1922 - Oct. 3, 1934
  - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1923-1938 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Code No. 8-184, pt. 1; Oct. 16, 1923 - Dec. 28, 1938
  - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Code No. 8-184, pt. 2; Jan. 6, 1938 - Jan. 6, 1939
  - Maine Central Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Code No. 8-185, pt. 1; Nov. 30, 1923 - Aug. 17, 1934
  - Nickel Plate Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Code No. 8-186; Oct. 25, 1923 - Nov. 24, 1934
  - Nickel Plate Railroad, 1925-1928 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Code No. 8-186a; Mar. 23, 1925 - May 31, 1928
  - Philadelphia and Reading Railroad, 1923-1937 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Code No. 8-187; Oct. 15, 1923 - Jul. 22, 1937
  - Jacksonville Terminal Company, 1922-1934 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Code No. 8-188; Jul. 12, 1922 - May 29, 1934
  - Colorado and Southern Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Code No. 8-189; Oct. 15, 1923 - Aug. 29, 1934